Viewers all over the world, we know you are there and we know that you are with us
Right now, it is time to release all souls under the bondage, dominion of demons, sickness and disease.
It is time to release you!
Believing is our connection.
All souls under the bondage, whatever bondage that you are in -
dominion of demons, sickness, disease and affliction,
receive freedom in the name of Jesus!
Receive freedom in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name
Receive freedom in the name of Jesus!
Many are in the cage; they just need to get out of their cage and discover themselves.
Dominion of sickness, demons, afflictions - receive freedom!
Be delivered! Be healed!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name
I can see you being delivered right now, this is the voice of God.
I can see you being delivered!
Viewers, I can see you being healed!
Receive your freedom in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name
All souls under bondage, dominion of demons with all his afflictions,
with all of his sicknesses and diseases -
be free!
Receive freedom!
Receive freedom, in the name Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name
Viewers all over the world,
we know by the power of the Holy Ghost, that you might have eaten many things
from the table of the enemy in your dream that is causing you bad luck, and backwardness,
affliction and disease, begin to flush them out of your blood in the name of Jesus!
By the blood of Jesus!
By the power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name
Flush them out!
Viewers all over the world, in the name of Jesus,
all knees shall bow and all tongues shall confess.
Receive freedom!
Freedom!
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.